<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Project name="TvT_KoeniglicherKampf_project">
	<Package name="TvT_KoeniglicherKampf_package">

		<Container name="mission briefing">
			<Key ID="str_GRAD_story">
				<Original>2083. 13 years ago Chinese computer scientists achieved a breakthrough in AI research. The first of its kind computer program that met all the criteria for what futurologists of the early 2000s called Strong AI. Overpopulation and increasing automation of the world's industry has widened the gap between the rich and the poor. Billions of people are being kept on the verge of starvation. A socio scientific paradigm shift called New Wave Darwinism has found more and more acceptance amongst the political elites. A new type of sport is gaining popularity, promising hopeless young males a chance for their family to enter the upper caste. It is called Königlicher Kampf and not Battle Royale or something.</Original>
				<English>2083. 13 years ago Chinese computer scientists achieved a breakthrough in AI research. The first of its kind computer program that met all the criteria for what futurologists of the early 2000s called strong AI. Overpopulation and increasing automation of the world's industry has widened the gap between the rich and the poor. Billions of people are being kept on the verge of starvation. A socio scientific paradigm shift called New Wave Darwinism has found more and more acceptance amongst the political elites. A new type of sport is gaining popularity, promising hopeless young males a chance for their family to enter the upper caste. A handful of players are dropped on a remote island with weapons of the 1990s and the early 2000s and fight for survival. It is called Königlicher Kampf and not Battle Royale or something.</English>
				<German>2083. Vor 13 Jahren geland Chinesischen Informatikern ein Durchbruch in der KI-Forschung. Das erste Computerprogramm seiner Art, was Futurologen der frühen 2000er Starke KI genannt hätten. Überbevölkerung und zunehmende Automatisierung der weltweiten Industrie hat die Kluft zwischen Arm und Reich vergrößert und Milliarden Menschen an den Rand der Existenz gedrängt. Ein sozialwissenschaftlicher Paradigmenwechsel, genannt New Wave Darwinism, hat mehr und mehr Anklang in der politischen Elite gefunden. Eine neue Art von Sport erfreut sich zunehmender Beliebtheit und verheißt hoffnungslosen, jungen Männern eine Chance mit ihrer Familie in die obere Kaste aufzusteigen. Eine Handvoll Spieler werden mit Waffen der 1990er und der frühen 2000er auf einer verlassenen Insel ausgesetzt und kämpfen ums Überleben. Man nennt sie Königlicher Kampf.</German>
			</Key>

			<Key ID="str_GRAD_brief2title">
				<Original>Gameplay</Original>
				<English>Gameplay</English>
				<German>Spielablauf</German>
			</Key>

			<Key ID="str_GRAD_gameplay">
				<Original>You and your teammates will be dropped together over a random position inside the playarea. Use your parachute. Try to keep your landing speed below 20 km/h and avoid any objects on the ground. Find weapons and equipment inside buildings. Stay inside the playzone (black circle | only on some maps) at all times. Over the duration of the game, a blue circle will appear that shrinks every X minutes. Whenever your map is updated with a new circle, a message will tell you how long you have to get inside. Should you still be outside after that time, you will slowly take damage until you are back inside. The team that survives the longest wins. There are boats and cars distributed randomly across the playarea. In random intervals red supply boxes will be dropped by parachute that contain rare loot. If you die, you will be able to spectate the remaining players.</Original>
				<English>You and your teammates will be dropped together over a random position inside the playarea. Use your parachute. Try to keep your landing speed below 20 km/h and avoid any objects on the ground. Find weapons and equipment inside buildings. Stay inside the playzone (black circle | only on some maps) at all times. Over the duration of the game, a blue circle will appear that shrinks every X minutes. Whenever your map is updated with a new circle, a message will tell you how long you have to get inside. Should you still be outside after that time, you will slowly take damage until you are back inside. The team that survives the longest wins. There are boats and cars distributed randomly across the playarea. In random intervals red supply boxes will be dropped by parachute that contain rare loot. If you die, you will be able to spectate the remaining players.</English>
				<German>Deine Teamkameraden und du werden über einer zufälligen Position innerhalb der Spielzone zusammen abgeworfen. Benutze deinen Fallschirm. Versuche deine Landegeschwindigkeit unter 20 km/h zu halten und vermeide auf Objekten zu landen. Finde Waffen und Equipment in Gebäuden. Bleibe innerhalb der Spielzone (schwarzer Kreis | nur auf manchen Karten). Im Verlauf des Spieles wird ein blauer Kreis auf deiner Karte eingetragen werden, der schrittweise kleiner wird. Jedes mal wenn deine Karte ein Update bekommt erscheint eine Nachricht, die dir sagt wie lange du Zeit hast, um in den neuen blauen Kreis zu kommen. Solltest du nach Ablauf dieser Zeit noch außerhalb des Kreises sein, nimmst du langsam Schaden bis du wieder drin ist. Das Team, was am längsten überlebt, gewinnt. Es gibt Boote und Fahrzeuge, die zufällig in der Spielzone verteilt sind. In unregelmäßigen Abständen werden rote Kisten per Fallschirm abgeworfen, die seltene Waffen und Equipment enthalten. Wenn du stirbst kannst du den restlichen Spielern zuschauen.</German>
			</Key>
		</Container>

		<Container name="mission setup">
		</Container>

	</Package>
</Project>
